Ahmed Derbali

JUNIOR FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



□ ahmedder@live.fr

+216 58 02 19 04

Mourouj-5, Ben Arous

26/07/1993 ► Tunisien

Army Captain in ahmed-derbali

DerbaliA

△ About Me

Languages

Coming from a background development, I love creating pages where I'm able to create enjoyable interactions and experiences everyone! And with Coding Dojo's education and support, I can now call myself a junior Full-stack Web Developer... spending eight years working as an army officer taught me how to lead a group and many other soft skills like Punctuality, Deliberation, Practicality, and Imperturbability...

English IELTS	
French TCF	
German Goethe-Institute	
Arabic Native	

Interests & Hobbies

Coding | Cycling | Mindfulness Camping

Education

Full-stack Web Development, *Coding Dojo (American Certification)* 12/2022 – present

• Web Fundamentals / Python / JavaScript / Java

Master's Degree in Military Science, *The Military Academy* 2015 – 2017

- Military Subjects: Arms / Ammunition / Ballistic /Shooting /...
- University Subjects: Finance / Math / Economics / Languages /...

Fundamental License Degree in Finance,

Faculty of Economics and Management of Tunis 2012 – 2015

- Case Study / Corporate Recording / Strategic Business Management /...
- Audit and Assurance / Tax Compliance / Financial Management / Business Planning / Financial Accounting and Reporting / Business Strategies and Technologies /...
- Accounting / Management Information / Principles of Taxation / Law /...

Technical Skills

Web Fundamentals

(Terminal - Git /GitHub - HTML5 - CSS3 - JavaScript - jQuery)

Python

(Python 3 - OOP - Flask - MySQL - Ajax)

JavaScript

(JavaScript ES6 - MongoDB - Express.js - React - Node.js - Socket.io - Tailwind (Framework))

Java

(Java 8 - MySQL - JSP - Spring Data JPA - Spring Boot - Spring Security - Bootstrap (Framework))

Professional Experience

A Company Commander of the Military Academy, *Tunisian Army* 07/2022 – present

An Instructor at the Military Engineering Training Center, *Tunisian Army* 07/2022 – 07/2023

A Company Commander of the Engineering Corps, *Tunisian Army* 07/2021 – 07/2022

A Platoon Leader of Engineering Corps, *Tunisian Army* 08/2017 – 07/2021

Projects

Computers Shop, A Template with only HTML and CSS.

• a company's website selling computers and laptops...

jQuery Travel Theme Website Template

 Wonder Tour is an excellent free HTML5 template which is ideal for a travel agency website.

Derbali_E-Commerce_Shop, MERN Stack

An e-commerce website using MongoDB, Express js, React, node js, and Tailwind CSS as a Framework

Responsive Blog App, MERN Stack

Responsive MERN Stack App with React, Node.JS, Express JS MongoDB JWT Authentication and File Upload.